Hadi Lashkari Ghouchani

Android Developer

@ hadilashkari@gmail.com

+98 939 125 8116

O Tehran Iran

github.com/hadilg

stackoverflow.com/users/2482947 in linkedin.com/in/hadilg

Summary

A curious developer with over 14 years of experience in software development, where almost 4 years of his experience covers Android development, over 2 years covers teaching algorithms and programming in universities, and over 8 years covers academic and self-employed experiences while he was a student.

An introvert person who has profound learning and contributing skills. A creative, value driven and passionate developer who enjoys doing math, solving problems and creating scalable, maintainable, and efficient apps to make the world better place to live.

A person whose goal is to surround himself with happy, creative, motivative and clever persons, so his talent becomes flourished.

He's interested in Data Science and Data Engineering so currently he's looking forward to learn TensorFlow

Experience

Lead Android Developer

m Jan. 2018 - Jan. 2019

Sheypoor is one of two lead classified marketplaces in Iran with 1.5+ million users per day, 13+ million overall users and 344+ million sessions.

Missions:

- Increase the number of users per day from 0.5+ million to 1.5+ million in a year.
- As functional manager of the Android team, he was responsible for the code quality of the Sheypoor app. He coached the team to practice design patterns, clean code, and using app architecture, along with updating libraries and adding new features with focus on agility and UX.
- · Implementing new design of the entire app, including rebranding for summer campaign.
- Improving the legacy code quality by adding Dagger and Kotlin.

Technologies

- Dagger 2, RxJava 2, Butter Knife, Greendao, etc.
- · Agile, Kanban, Git Flow, CI/CD
- Mockito Espresso Jacoco
- Pivotal Tracker, Github, Jenkins, Slack, Zeplin, etc.

Senior Android Developer

at Myket

O Tehran, Iran

Myket is one of two lead app stores in Iran with over 8+ million users.

- Starting TDD and installing Jenking's pipeline to handle CI/CD.
- Implementing features such as handling deeplinks, search page, inbox page, etc.

Technologies:

- Volley, OneSignal, EventBus, OrmLite, etc.
- · Agile, Scrum, Git Flow
- Atlassian Jira, Atlassian Confluence, Gitlab, Jfrog, Jenkins

Java and C# developer

at Soha System

mar. 2015 - Aug. 2015

Tehran, Iran

SOHA is formed to focus on solutions based on smart cards.

- Implementing RFID card reader Android app via bluetooth connection.
- Implementing Android and desktop apps.

Lecturer

at Universities

m Feb. 2012 - Dec. 2014

Mashhad Iran

After two years of enrollment by conscription, he had been working in two universities, Payame Noor University and Sadjad University of Technology.

Application of Computers in Physics, Mathematical Physics, etc.

Article

ProAndroidDev post: Logging in Kotlin ProAndroidDev post: Reactive MVVM architectural pattern

ProAndroidDev post: Loading entities from database and server API by using RxJava ProAndroidDev post: LiveData with single events

Education

Sharif University Of Technology Payame Noor University

M.Sc B.Sc

in Physics in Physics 🛗 Jul. 2007

Tehran Mashhad

Tools / Skills

Android

Android Architecture Components/JetPack Lifecycles/LiveData/Navigation/Paging ViewModel/WorkManager Dagger 2/RxJava 2/Retrofit 2/... Butter Knife/ObjectBox/.

Architecture

Clean Architecture/Hexagonal Architecture MVVM, MVP, RMVVM

Principle

Clean Code/SOLID Object Oriented Programming Functional Programming Stable Dependencies Principle Stable Abstractions Principle

Design Pattern

Factory/Builder/Singleton/... Adapter/Facade/Proxy/. Strategy/Chain of responsibility/...

Android test library

JUnit/Mockito/Espresso/Jacoco/...

Build Tool

Gradle/Maven/Ant/Make/...

Command Line Tool

grep/sed/netstat/awk/docker/... adb/sdkmanager/avdmanager/...

Development Tool

Pivotal Tracker/Jira/Jenkins/..

Programing Language

Java/Kotlin/Scala/Python Groovy/Dart/Javascript/Rust/...

Operating System

Linux(Fedora/Ubuntu/Debian), OS X

Special Honor

- Ranked 44th among more than five thousand participants in the National Graduate Entrance Exam in Physics at Spring 2007.
- Received result-oriented badge in Sheypoor at 2018

Language

English: Advance Farsi: Native

The source of this res Built at February 27, 2019